http://lollipoptheater.org/privacy-policy

Lollipop Theater Network Donor Privacy Policy
We respect the privacy of our donors, those who support Lollipop Theater Network (LOLLIPOP) with a financial or in-kind contribution. It is our policy:
Choice and Consent: To respect the purpose for which our donors gave us information. We give donors the option to have mail and email sent to them from LOLLIPOP or to opt out of these activities.
Information Collection: The LollipopTheater.org web site will collect personally identifiable information (such as name, title, company name or e-mail address) that you voluntarily provide when you donate through our website or e-mail correspondence. We will collect general information (such as the type of browser you use, the files you request, and the domain name and country from which you request information) to improve our website and better meet your needs.
Use of Information: The information you supply when you donate will be used by Lollipop Theater Network (LOLLIPOP) and the LollipopTheater.org web site to respond to your inquiries, supply you with requested information, and further our activities. Authorized third parties may be utilized by the LollipopTheater.org web site to collect, track, and process such information for the benefit of the LollipopTheater.org web site. By law, Lollipop Theater Network is required to file an annual non-profit organization tax return, IRS Form 990. Although the Form 990 is considered public information and may be found posted on the LollipopTheater.org web site and various charity rating sites, donor names are specifically excluded from the information available for public inspection.
Third Party Use: We do not EVER sell, rent, or loan our donor lists to third parties for marketing of any kind, mail or email.
Unsubscriptions: We send our information only to those who request it (that is, opt-in). We immediately unsubscribe those who request it through convenient unsubscribe links in every e-mailing or by phone, email or mail request made directly to the foundation. Our thank you and welcome message to donors and every issue of our reports/e-mails clearly explain how to unsubscribe.
Security: We store donor and password files with personal information in a secure manner. We store such files in areas not accessible to Web browsers, behind password protection and firewalls, or off-line.
The LollipopTheater.org web site reserves the right to modify this donor privacy policy at any time. We will promptly reflect any such modifications in these web pages.
If you have any concerns or questions about our Donor Privacy Policy or information collected, please Contact Us or call us at (310) 235-2772 and we will reply promptly.
Lollipop
Home
Who We Are
Overview
About Us
Our History
Our Team
The Board
Lollipop Theater Network 7461 Beverly Blvd.
Stay Informed!Join our mailing list to receive the latest LOLLIPOP news and updates
SUBSCRIBE!
You have Successfully Subscribed!
